漫威《神盾局特工》前情回顾
Previously on "Marvel's Agents Of S.H.I.E.L.D."...
所以你觉得巨石是个传送门
So you think the rock is a portal?
是时空中的一道裂缝  带走了西蒙斯
A crack in space-time that carried Simmons away...
去了另一个星球
to another planet.
菲兹
Fitz!
也就是说
Which means...
她就在那里
She's out there.
九头蛇已四分五裂
Hydra's fractured, in pieces.
我们要重建它  好好重建
We're gonna rebuild it... the right way...
-你想怎么打入  -从下方
- What's your way in? - From below.
一步步往上爬  九头蛇万岁什么的
Climb the ranks. Hail Hydra and all that.
我要从这些军火贩那里抢一批弹头
I'm gonna nab a payload from these gunrunners
好建立伪装身份
to establish my cover.
我知道你想在这里建立生活
I get that you're trying to build a life here...
是啊  正常生活  你就别来插手了
Yes, a normal life, so stay out of it,
建立了一支特遣队
I have created a special task force
ATCU  专门应对美国本土的外星威胁
the ATCU, to neutralize these alien threats on our soil.
跟我们走吧
Come with us.
我们能保护你  你现在有危险
We'll keep you safe. Your life is in danger.
我的生活毁了
My life is in ruins.
他在朝北边跑
He's moving north!
有必要可进行致命打击
Use lethal force if necessary!
我跟住他了
I'm on his trail.
快走
Move it, move it!
那边
There.
站住
Stop!
后退
Fall back!
第二小组试着拦截他
Unit two ?can try and head him off.
给她打电话
But get her on the phone.
告诉她我们跟丢了
Tell her we lost him.
得叫上所有人了
It's time to bring ?everyone in on this.
西蒙斯不必被隔离
Simmons didn't have to go through quarantine,
总的来说  这是好事
which is good, all things considered.
我们究竟要考虑些什么
What exactly are these things that we're considering?
在另一个星球上待了数月的一切可能后果
Everything that comes with being on another planet for months.
不同的大气层  不同水平的氧化
Different atmosphere, different levels of oxygenation,
不同的微重力
different microgravity.
她体内的所有系统都紊乱了
Every system in her body's out of whack.
心血管  内耳  呼吸系统
Cardiovascular, inner ear, respiratory
都已经习惯了另一个地方
all got used to being... not here.
实验室结果显示她有氧化应激症  缺乏维生素D
Labs indicate oxidative stress, vitamin D deficiency,
上呼吸道刺激
upper-respiratory irritation.
她有提到生命体吗  智慧生命或者别的
Any mention of life, intelligent or otherwise?
有些植物  没有动物
Some flora, no fauna.
她说她在被追杀
She said she was being hunted.
等等  什么   什么意思
Wait. What? What does that mean?
被什么追杀
Hunted by what?
她没说  我都不确定她自己是否知道
She didn't say. I don't know if she even knows. ?
天哪
My god.
想想她一个人经历了那一切  还那么久
Imagine her having to go through all that alone for that long.
多亏了这家伙  她回来了
Well, thanks to this guy, not anymore.
监测她的身体健康
Monitor her physical health.
我和加纳博士通了电话
I've got a call in to Dr. Garner.
她的心理健康同样重要
Her mental health is just as important.
但别逼她
But don't push her.
准备好后她会说的
She'll open up when she's ready.
林肯有麻烦了
Lincoln's in trouble.
ATCU发布了一条全国警戒
The ATCU issued a nationwide BOLO...
联调局  国土安全部  地方警察
FBI, homeland security, local police...
都收到了通知
all notified.
发给了他们林肯的简历和头像
Sent 'em Lincoln's résumé and head shot.
听起来ATCU不顾一切了
Sounds like the ATCU's getting desperate.
找到他后他们要干吗
What are they gonna do when they find him?
肯定没好事  他需要帮助
I'm guessing it won't be awesome. He needs help.
我们找过林肯不止一次了
Look, we went to Lincoln more than once.
他不要我们帮忙
He didn't want our help.
那不代表他就该像个逃犯一样被追捕
It doesn't mean he deserves to be hunted like a fugitive,
更何况还有个充满怨恨的巨人
not to mention there's a giant with a grudge
想要杀他呢
looking to kill him.
所以咱们得带他回来  刻不容缓
Which is why we need to bring him in -- now.
那也得知道他在哪才行
That would be the plan if we knew where to find him,
可他不回我信息  而且我...
But he's not messaging me back, and I --
怎么了
What?
要不你来告诉她
You want to tell her?
好吧  告诉我什么
Great. Tell me what?
你俩有什么事都不想告诉我
What do neither of you want to tell me?
我们知道怎么找他
We know how to find him.
林肯  是我
Lincoln, it's me.
黛西
Daisy?
你怎么知道这号码的
How the hell did you get this number?
这不重要
That's not important.
现在重要的是你得找个安全的地方
What's important right now is that you get somewhere safe.
这电话是我刚买的
I just bought this phone.
我知道
Yes, I know.
35分钟前  在71街和宾福德街一家酒铺买的
35 minutes ago at a liquor store at 71st and Binford.
你知道我在哪
You know where I am?
知道  而且我说服了他们让我先跟你谈...
Yes, and I convinced them to let me talk to you before --
真不敢相信你会这么做
I can't believe you would do this.
林肯  听我说完  好吗
Just -- Lincoln, just hear me out, okay?
ATCU已经把你的照片发给了执法机关
The ATCU has released your picture to law enforcement.
现在到处都在缉拿你
It's everywhere, calling for your arrest.
我们会来接你
We're gonna come get you.
林肯
Lincoln?
我搭档没说完你别想走
You're not walking out of here till my partner has said her piece.
他肯定把追踪器烧了
He must have blown his tracker.
当然  因为他对自己被装了追踪器感到害怕
Yeah, because he's creeped out that you put a tracker in him.
是啊  要不是她告诉了他
Yeah, and if she didn't give him a heads-up,
我们就能利用追踪器把他带回来了
we could have used it to bring him in.
他已经很恐慌  疑神疑鬼了
He's already scared, paranoid.
搞突然袭击只会适得其反
Ambushing him out of nowhere would have made things way worse.
那他就可以在我们这里释放他的情绪
And he would have been able to express those feelings
而这里很安全
to us here, secure in our location.
好了  大家都别紧张
All right, all right. Everybody, just relax.
我们会有办法的
We'll figure this out.
马萨诸塞州  阿尔斯顿
他应该在这里
He should be in here.
我们之前一起合作过
We did a couple of jobs together a while back.
他在英国时和九头蛇关系密切
He's tight with Hydra in the U.K.
搬到美国之后
And continued his association
还继续跟他们有联系
when he relocated here to the U.S.
他在那儿
There he is.
你先请
You lead.
斯巴德
Spud.
怎么会  瑞奇
Why, here's Richy!
真没想到啊
As I live and breathe!
胡子挺帅啊
?Working the bum fluff.
吉娜  这是斯巴德
Oh, G-Gina, Spud.
斯巴德  这是吉娜
Spud, Gina.
你这种人也能泡到这种美女
Classy for the likes of you, eh?
只是生意伙伴
Business associates.
来抱一抱
Come here.
第一轮酒算我的
First round's on me.
好极了
Oh, nice one. ?
瑞奇跟我们说如果有货出手
Uh, so, Richy tells us you're the guy to go to
-找你就对了  -别着急
- if we need to unload-- ?- Hold your horses.
不是这么干的
That's not how it's done.
先喝酒  然后再谈生意
First we drink, then we talk business.
来三杯扎啤
Three pints.
好吧  因为你们还不够难以理解
Right, 'cause you guys aren't hard enough to understand as it is.
糟糕透了
我们坐在拉驴的车里
我和这个家伙
后面是五十条黑市买来的镀镉钢
然后收音机里
你小心点
播起了《爱痕》那首歌  知道那首歌吗
播起了那首歌  而这家伙
这家伙鼻涕眼泪一把流
滚边
那时我未婚妻刚跑了  把我一个人丢下
我都崩溃了
十个小时里  每次那歌一响起
他都哭得抖成一团
是你反复放那首歌  你个笨蛋
说得没错
Yeah, you're right.
我是那么干了
I did, didn't I?
经典的公路旅行啊
And, man, classic road trip.
行了
All right.
他是个白痴
He's a muppet.
如果我们再不进入正题
But if we don't start talking shop soon,
他就要喝醉了  所以...
he's gonna pass out, so --
你有什么要出手的吗
You have something to unload?
新式武器  杀伤力一流
Weapons -- next gen, high potential damage.
我们要的是唯恐天下不乱的有钱买家
We need buyers with deep pockets and bad intentions.
你自然也有佣金拿
A finder's fee for you, of course.
我认识些人...
I know people...
但他们疑心极重
But they have massive trust issues.
他们要什么  推荐信吗
What do they want -- a letter of recommendation?
靠我担保是不够的
?Me vouching won't be enough.
那要怎么的  花钱买路吗
Well, what is? Do I buy my way in?
不是
No.
你要打进去
You fight your way in.
如果你是最后站着的人
If you are the last man standing,
他们就见你
you'll get a meeting.
貌似挺有趣
Sounds like a laugh.
该疑犯是危险分子
The suspect is considered dangerous.
同时受到联邦当局和ATCU的通缉
And he is wanted by both Federal authorities and the ATCU.
事态真是急转直下
This just went from bad to really, really bad.
他们公开了
They've gone public.
如看到此人  切勿与其交手
If you do see this man, do not engage.
另一则新闻  辛辛那提医院
In other news, a suspect has been identified
外星恐怖袭击中的嫌疑人身份已确认
in the Cincinnati hospital alien terrorist attack
袭击造成三人死亡  多人受伤
that left three dead, many more injured.
如果您有照片中此人的消息
If you have any information about the man pictured here,
请联系有关部门
be sure to contact the authorities.
你就是那个人
You're him.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know ?what you're talking about.
我看见你了
I saw you.
我知道你是什么
I know what you are.
你根本不知道
You have no idea.
黛西  你去监控林肯最后出现地点
Daisy, I need you to monitor all law enforcement
附近的执法部门的一举一动
near Lincoln's last known location.
不如我们自己带一队人去找他
How about we take a team, go look for ourselves?
不行  ATCU正到处无故抓捕异能人士
No, the ATCU's on a witch hunt for powered people.
我可不怕他们
I'm not afraid of them.
你是不怕  但他们怕你
No, but they're terrified of you,
这让他们非常危险
which makes them dangerous.
在我们找到他之前你都不能行动
Till we know where he is, you're not going out there.
能说说想法吗
Permission to speak freely.
我有得选吗
Do I have a choice?
如果你没擅自给他植入皮下跟踪器
I could have talked him in if you didn't put
我本可劝他自己投降的
an unsolicited tracker under his skin.
如果你没打电话警告他  那我们...
If you didn't call to alert him, then we --
为什么没跟我说
Why wasn't I told?
我们觉得这事对你来说太切身了
We thought you were a little close to the situation.
当然了
Of course ?I'm close to the situation.
你让我组建一支队伍  我领了任务
You asked me to assemble a team, and I accepted.
我没料到会遭到掣肘
I didn't expect to be undermined and --
你知道什么是我始料不及的吗
Do you know what I didn't expect?
全球异人族爆发
A global outbreak.
ATCU  他们对异人族的追捕
The ATCU, ?their inhuman manhunt --
老实讲  我没料到这会发生
I didn't see all that coming, to be honest.
我想要组建队伍  控制局面
I wanted to assemble a team, to get ahead of the problem,
但事与愿违
but that didn't happen.
所以  黛西
So, Ddaisy...
我去监控执法部门通讯
I'll scan law-enforcement channels.
谢谢
Thank you.
迈克  是你查明了罗莎琳・普莱斯的身份
Mack, you were able to identify Rosalind Price's photo.
能给我拿到她的电话吗
?How about getting me her digits?
没问题
You got it.
还在适应重力较小的环境
Still acclimating to less gravity.
这画面真让人开心
Well, now, this is a sight for sore eyes.
我想回到实验室可能有点帮助
Thought it would be good to get back in the lab,
看看老地方
see the old workspace.
就是那个吗
Is that it?
它原来是传送门
It was the portal.
现在是一堆太空岩石
Now it's a pile of space rocks.
我做过了完整彻底的检测
I've run a complete and exhaustive set of diagnostics,
可以向你保证这无须担心
so I can assure you there's no need to worry.
你还好吗
You okay?
-还好  -先失陪了
- Fine. - ?Just a sec.
亨特打来的  他在追捕沃德
It's Hunter. He's on a Ward hunt.
代我问好
Say "Hi."
当然
You know it.
你看
Hey, look.
和你离开时一样
Just as you left it --
就连便贴的位置都没变
Made sure not even a post-it note was moved,
因为我知道你对这些多讲究
'cause I know how particular you can be about it.
怎么了
What is it?
我只是...
Um, I'm just...
有这么多杂七杂八的东西不太适应
I'm not accustomed ?to this many distractions.
我想你之前肯定都看花眼了
Yeah, well, I imagine you must have had quite a lot to take in --
要检查外星物质和样本
extraterrestrial materials and specimens to examine.
我一害怕  好奇心就消失了
My curiosity faded once fear set in.
对啊
Right.
不  当然了
Yeah, no, of course.
抱歉
Sorry.
我得承认  这有点不好承受
Uh, I have to admit -- it's all a bit much.
你介意吗
Would you mind?
不  怎么  要我叫芭比来吗
?Uh, yeah. What -- should I get Bobbi?
不
No.
就是有点晕乎乎的
Um, it's just a little disorientation,
可能是因为氧化应激
attributable to oxidative stress.
好  我带你回房间
Okay, yeah, I'll take you back to your room.
希望你不会对我太失望
I hope you're not too disappointed.
不  正相反  你在自我诊断
No, on the contrary, you're self-diagnosing,
说明你在好转
which is a sign you're on the mend.
她现在怎么样了
And how is she now?
你要是困在另一个太阳系中几个月
As weirded out as you'd be after being stranded for months
-也会变得一样奇怪  -我得说
- in another Solar System. - ?Oh, I must say --
总部似乎比我们这边有趣多了
HQ sounds a lot more fun than what we're up to.
我怎么就不相信你呢
Now, why don't I believe you?
你为什么听起来宿醉未醒
And why do you sound hung over?
因为我确实宿醉了
Because I am hung over.
在这儿除了喝酒就没别的事可做了
There's nothing to do here but drink.
飞机  火车  汽车  追踪线索
Planes, trains, and automobiles, chasing down leads --
还是没发现沃德的踪迹
Still no sign of Ward.
你没做什么蠢事吧
So, you're not doing anything stupid?
还没
Mm, not yet.
但有一辆火车要出发了
But one of those trains is about to leave the station,
我得赶上那趟车
and I need to get on it.
那祝你好运
Well, good luck.
别死了
Don't die.
我只会无聊死
Only thing I'll die of is boredom.
你对她撒谎了
You lied to her.
不算是
Barely.
而且她知道我在撒谎
Besides, she knows I'm lying,
所以这不能算是说谎
so it's not even really a lie.
这样适合我们  目前是这样
Works for us... For now.
你知道的  这些事很复杂
You know how complicated these things can be --
感情的事  尤其对干我们这行的来说
Affairs of the heart, especially in our line of work.
我和芭比
Me and Bob.
你和安德鲁
You and Andrew.
你信任斯巴德吗
So, do you trust spud?
对一个疯子  没有信任之说
"Trust"'s a strong word for a psychopath.
他是个杀人强盗
He's a murderous thief
我见过他把一个人的鼻子全咬掉了
who I once saw ?bite a man's nose clean off.
但他会帮我们进门的
But he'll get us through the door.
有件事挺逗
You'll find this funny.
之前在总部  我们可是有赌约
Back at H.Q., ?we've got a little wager going
关于你和博士之间的事
on what happened between you and the good doctor.
我猜是你离开了  不是因为生气或什么
My guess is you walked away -- not in a huff or anything,
而是受不了没完没了地聊天  分享
just couldn't stand ?the constant talking, sharing.
这倒是真的  我不喜欢说太多
It's true. ?I don't like a lot of talking.
这场仗  是我们接近沃德的唯一办法
This fight -- it's our way to Ward,
所以如果你加入  就得赢
so if you're gonna do this, you need to win.
你是觉得我赢不了吗
Are you suggesting I can't win?
我不是说你不行  但我知道我能赢
I'm not saying you can't, but I know I can.
斯巴德交的都是一种人
Spud runs with a type.
那种人看到一个小个亚洲女人
If that type see a small Asian woman
赤手空拳地打败了想加入九头蛇的恶棍
destroy some wannabe Hydra thug in a bare-knuckle brawl,
他们会说出去的
that type will talk.
而话可能会往上传
And word might spread up the ranks.
我明白
I see your point.
你只是离开太久
You're just anxious to bash some heads
急着想找人打
after being out of the game.
听着
Look.
我清醒时已经输了一场
I've rarely lost a fight when I'm sober,
我打算保持清醒的
which I plan on being.
我经得住打  即便是糟糕情况
And I can take a punch, so worst case,
我就等到对方打疲了再说
I'll do that ?till the other guy tires out.
你在我离开安德鲁这个赌上
So... How much do you have
压了多少钱
riding on this bet that I left Andrew?
不少呢
A significant sum.
好吧
Well...
你输了
You lost it.
你喝酒了吗
Have you been drinking?
我想的
I wanted to.
但我没有  而是打给了你
Instead, I called you.
你是我唯一信任的人
You're the only one I trust.
上车
Get in.
这趟车搭的可不近啊
It's a hell of a long way for a ride.
我知道
I know.
回去的路费我包了
I'll take care of the tolls on the way back.
一路上你都在睡觉
You slept the whole drive.
我累坏了
I was pretty wiped out.
我有点想听听让你这么累的有趣经历
Yeah, I was kind of hoping for the hilarious tale of why.
你打电话不是为了让我劝你别喝酒
You didn't call to have me talk you off a ledge --
至少这次不是
Not this time, anyway.
林肯  到底发生了什么事
Linc, what's going on?
我惹上了点小麻烦
Ah, I'm in a little bit of trouble.
你可急死我了
You are killing me with these details.
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know.
只是个误会
Look, ?it's a misunderstanding.
我向你保证  我没做错任何事
I promise you, ?I haven't done anything wrong.
好  有这句话就够了
Okay, ?that is all I need to hear.
你知道你是什么样的人
I know ?what kind of man you are.
就告诉我你需要什么吧
Just tell me what you need.
我希望
I was hoping, uh...
你可以把车卖给我
You'd let me buy your car off of you.
我知道这不是小事
I know it's a lot to ask.
我会付现金
Uh, I-I'll pay cash.
成交
Done.
约翰  我不知道该说什么好
John, ?I don't know what to say.
没关系  稍等一下
All right, now, wait a minute.
你其实是在帮我
You're -- you're doing me a favor. It's a
我的车就是一堆废铜烂铁
pile of rust.
我来做点吃的  好吗
All right? I'll make us some dinner. I don't know.
你休息一下
Take a nap,
或者洗个澡  浴室就在那边
or the shower's over there, if you want to take a shower.
我家就是你家
Mi casa, su casa. ?
一切都会好起来的
It's gonna be okay.
通缉危险外星嫌犯
他不可能就那样消失了
?He didn't just disappear...
除非他真的能...
Unless he did.
但是他不能  对吧
Well, he can't do that, can he?
他不能  他的能力是电
No. Electric's his thing.
他会出现的
He'll show.
这就是我们公诸于众的原因
That's why we alerted the public.
他无处藏身了
He's got nowhere to hide.
希望如此
I hope so.
我们需要有进展  出成绩了
We need to start making progogress, showing results.
普莱斯女士  有你的电话
Ms. Price, you have a call.
等下再说
Well, it can wait.
是白宫打来的
It's the White House.
转到我屏幕上吧
Throw it up on my screen.
科尔森
Coulson.
叫我菲尔就行
Call me "Phil."
怎么也不能叫你美国总统吧
What I can't call you is POTUS.
你不是唯一在白宫有关系的人
You're not the only person with a connection to the White House.
我的关系是一个马上要被发现的
Well, mine's a pirated satellite connection
盗用卫星连接  所以我就长话短说了
that will be discovered soon, so I'll be brief.
你动静挺大啊
You're making a lot of noise,
说实话  我有点不高兴
and frankly, I'm a little insulted.
你在向所有人寻求帮助
You're asking everyone for help --
联调局  地方警察  连公众都惊动了
The FBI, local police, and now the public --
但是就没找真正的知情者
Everyone except the people who actually know something.
-你是说你吗  -就是说我
- You mean you. - ?That is what I mean, yes.
所以我觉得我们该见个面  就我们两个
So, I think we should meet, just the two of us --
面对面  找个中点
In person, neutral ground.
稍等我一下
Uh, will you excuse me for a moment?
我们找到林肯・坎贝尔了
We have a location on Lincoln Campbell.
他躲在芝加哥郊外一间公寓里
He's holed up in an apartment outside Chicago.
你知道该怎么做
You know what you need to do.
好吧  菲尔  我们见一面
Okay, Phil, let's meet.
我认为我们有很多东西可谈
I think we'll have a lot to talk about.
真不敢相信你回来了
I cannot believe you're here.
斯凯
Skye.
黛西  不好意思
Daisy. Sorry.
这是个多用途的礼物
It's a multipurpose gift.
既漂亮又能让你想起我
It's pretty and a reminder.
你怎么叫我都可以
You can call me whatever you want.
我不能待太久
I can't stay for too long.
我在监听执法部门的通讯
I'm tracking law-enforcement channels,
但很抱歉我没有早点来看你
but I am really sorry that I haven't come sooner.
就是  最近事情太多了
It's -- there's just a lot going on.
-而且我在一直睡  -这很好
- And I've been sleeping. - Which is good.
你要努力快点好起来
Do whatever you need to get better.
我们需要你
We need you.
我
And I...
我知道你还不想说发生的事
I know you don't want to talk about what happened yet,
但如果你想说  我愿意倾听
But when you do, I'm here for whatever you need.
现在我更想听你说
Right now I'd rather listen.
泰瑞根在扩散吗
The terrigen is spreading?
人们的怀疑也在加剧
So's the paranoia.
和顶层套房的风景不能比
Not exactly the penthouse view.
你在找什么吗
You looking for something?
不是  我只是  很难放松下来
No, I just -- ?it's hard to relax, you know?
我懂
I know.
一切还好吧
Everything okay?
能出什么事呢
Why wouldn't it be?
也许我该去冲个澡
Maybe I will hop in the shower.
约翰  怎么了
John, what's up?
出什么事了
What's wrong?
你站着别动  别碰我
You just stay where you are. Don't touch me.
等等  发生什么事了
Wait. What is going on?
他们很快就来了
They'll be here any minute.
你给谁打了电话
Who did you call?
我打了热线电话
I called the hotline.
他们说你是危险人物
They said that you're dangerous.
林肯  他们说你杀了人
Lincoln, they said that you killed people.
我没杀过人  我发誓
I never killed anyone -- I swear.
你说过你了解我是什么样的人
You said ?you know what type of man I am.
我连你到底是什么都不知道
I don't even know what you are.
他们说你是外星人
They say you're an alien.
完全不是你想的那样
It's not at all what you think.
你别动  别动  我没开玩笑
You just stay there. Stay there! I'm not kidding!
别动  他们随时会来
Stay there. They're gonna be here any minute.
给你
Here.
我把钱留下来  开车走人
I'm gonna leave the money and take the car.
你没必要牵扯进来
You don't need to be involved.
你别过来
Just stay back!
别挡着我
Get out of my way!
对不起我把你牵扯了进来
Sorry I brought you into this.
不要
No.
不  不  不
No, no, no, no.
不  约翰
No, John.
拜托  约翰
Come on, john!
你真的没事吗
You're really okay?
我觉得没事  我...
I think so. I'm...
只是...
Well, it's just that...
只是有些事很难说出口  还有
There's some of it that's hard to talk about, and, um...
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.
没事  接吧
No. Take it.
黛西
Daisy.
林肯  真对不起
Lincoln, I am so sorry.
我真不知道追踪器的事  否则
I-I had no idea about the tracker, and if I did, I...
别管那个了
?Don't worry about that now.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我需要帮助
I need help.
他不在
He's not here.
林肯躲起来了  他在等我们
Lincoln's hiding. He's waiting for us.
我们得带他回来
We need to bring him in,
最好不被ATCU察觉
preferably without the ATCU knowing.
虽然他刚杀了人吗
Even though he just killed a guy.
我说了  是个意外
I told you... it was an accident.
等他来了我们再说吧
We'll figure it out once we get him in here.
如果让麦克来处理撤离会更安全
It'd be safer if Mack handled the extraction.
我知道  但那样他就不会去了  必须我来
I know, but then he won't come. It's got to be me.
你决定
Your call.
你去哪
And where are you going?
海滩
To the beach.
能出勤我什么都愿意做
I'd give anything to be in the field.
复健是刺激的反义词
Rehab is the antithesis of exciting...
我很清楚  但是值得的
I'm well-aware, but it's worth it.
你看我还能说"反义词"这么绕口的词
You notice I was able to say "antithesis."
你去看西蒙斯了吗
You check on Simmons?
嗯
Yeah.
她有点
She's kind of...
疏远
distant.
我不知道怎么帮她
I'm not sure ?that I know how to help her.
我开始为膝盖做复健时
What did you drill into my head
你反复跟我说的是什么
when I started rehabbing my knee?
-要耐心  -没错
- Patience. - ?Exactly.
嗯  我知道
Yeah, I know. I know.
就是实验室...她很热爱实验室的
It's just the lab... she loved that lab,
设计全是按照她的具体要求
designed it according to her specifications.
可现在
Now it's...
或许这让她记起了以前
Could be it reminds her of the way things were...
和她失去的时间
...And all the time she lost.
是啊  这我没想过
Yeah. I didn't think of that.
别管那些她曾经在乎的东西了
Maybe forget about the things that used to matter to her.
给她点值得期待的东西
Give her something to look forward to.
重新开始
Start fresh.
嗯
Yeah.
或许你说得对  谢谢
Yeah, maybe you're right. Thanks.
不得不说  接到你电话时我很意外
Got to say, I was pretty surprised when I got your call.
看这里
Eyes up here.
被你发现了  抱歉
Busted. Sorry.
多谢你抽时间
I appreciate you taking the time.
说说我为什么要开到海边来
Gave me an excuse to drive up the coast.
她有名字吗
Does she have a name?
我爱我的车  但那也就是辆车
I love my car, but it's just a car.
而且是个他
And it's a him.
我们上次见面时
You know, last time we met,
你用你的逃脱手段缴了我的械
you, uh, disarmed me with your evasive tactics.
我明白你什么意思
I see what you did there.
不  我得承认
No, I got to hand it to you.
这让我好奇你还有什么本事
Makes me wonder what else you got up your sleeve.
不  我懂的
No, really, I get it.
忍不住
Hard to resist.
我不是第一个了吧
I assume I'm not the first.
你就是
I think you are.
这是新弄来的
It's fairly recent.
抱歉  肯定很不好受
Sorry. That can't be easy.
我们来不是为了讨论这个
That's not what ?we came here to discuss.
你采取的方式完全错了
You're going about this all wrong.
惊动公众  不明智
Panicking the public... not wise.
你再这么下去  情况会直转急下
Keep doing that, things are gonna get ugly real fast.
拉住他
Back him off!
他完了
He's done!
胜者产生
We got a winner!
没错
That's right!
好了  他完了  把他拖出去
All right, he's done, get him out of here!
下一个上  快点
Next man up, let's go, come on!
他还有气吗
Is he breathing?
那儿呢
There.
你没事吧
Are you good?
必须厉害的不是我
I'm not the one who needs to be good.
瑞奇来了  我们可以开始了
Richy's here. We can get started.
那个倒霉蛋是谁
Who's the unlucky sod, then?
你干什么
What the hell are you doing?
永远闭上你这张臭嘴
Shutting your stupid face up once and for all.
好了  就位
All right. In position.
你是开玩笑吗
Are you having a laugh?
我以为我们是朋友
I thought we were mates.
你想错了  你个傻蛋
You thought wrong, you mug.
好了
All right.
我们开始前需要了解什么规则吗
Oh, is there any rules I should know about before we start?
没有
Nope.
我们不就是开玩笑呢吗
We was having a laugh.
我可没笑
I wasn't laughing.
心里也没笑吗
Not even on the inside?
我请你喝杯酒吧
Let me get you a drink.
我不渴
I'm not thirsty.
再来一次  喝杯酒啊
Let's try that again. A drink?
还是不用
And again, no.
走吧
Come on.
肯定让你开心的
I promise you'll have a good time.
来吧
Come on.
谁先来
So... Who's first?
不如我帮你个忙  不告诉别人
How about I do you a favor and not tell anyone
你被一个矮小的亚洲女人痛扁了一顿
that a tiny, little asian woman kicked your ass?
你还不累吗
Are you not tired yet?
我本是想搞疲劳战术的
Because that was sort of my strategy.
来啊
Come on.
宣布胜负啊
Is somebody gonna call it?
有什么必要  他都没气了
What's the point? He's not breathing.
我们机构之所以存在就因为你们倒闭了
You know, my agency exists because yours imploded.
但我们回来了
But we came back,
虽然地盘小多了  也低调多了
albeit with less real estate and a lower profile.
低调就是问题所在
The low profile's the problem.
没人知道你们还在  但怪事却还在发生
No one knows you exist, but bizarre events keep happening.
人民需要有安全感
And people need to feel safe.
那么大张旗鼓地宣扬外星威胁
So all these APBs on alien threats...
是为了给人民安全感吗
those are ?to help people feel safe?
事实就是
Look, the truth is,
你根本不了解你对付的是什么
you don't understand what you're dealing with.
你就知道
And you do?
所以我求你让我的队伍把林肯带走
Which is why I'm asking you to let my team bring Lincoln in.
如果我们带走他  会容易点
If we take him, it'll be easy.
而你们去  会导致人受伤的
If you do it, people could get hurt.
或许如此  但是
That might be the case, but...
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我不能同意
I can't agree to that.
安全
Coast is clear.
是我
It's me.
你今天过得真够呛
You're having a hell of a day.
我
I, um...
我杀了他
I killed him.
约翰  他不止一次救过我
John, um, he saved my life more than once.
现在  我却救不了他
And now I couldn't bring him back.
他们说的关于我的一切都是对的
Everything they're saying about me is true.
他非常危险
He's extremely dangerous.
如果我们扣押他就不会有威胁了
He won't be if he's in our custody.
我们又不会采集他的器官
We're not gonna harvest him for parts,
如果你是担心这个
if that's ?what you're worried about.
我们不是九头蛇
We're not Hydra.
你现在这么说
You say that now.
他为什么那么重要
What's so important about him?
真的假的
Are you serious?
他能端掉一架飞机
He can bring down a plane.
值得找他聊一聊吧
Feels like a man worth talking to.
我有另一个想法
I have another theory.
总统大谈特谈了
The president makes a big speech
他组建的新机构
about this new organization he's put in place.
我猜这给了你不少压力吧
I imagine that puts ?a lot of pressure on you...
必须拿出成绩来
Pressure to show results.
没错
You're not wrong.
所以我要带走他
And that's why I'm taking him in.
但我们为什么来这儿  菲尔
But why are we here, Phil?
等着一起看日落吗
Are we waiting ?to watch the sunset together?
你如果不是来做交易的
'cause if you didn't come here to make a deal,
那你想要什么
then what do you want?
你手里有张王牌
You have an ace up your sleeve,
我不想再等你出手了
and I'm tired of waiting for you to play it.
是吗
Is that so?
你有医院的监控录像
You have surveillance from the hospital,
那么你就还有一张
which means there's another picture
没公布出去的照片
you chose not to put on TV.
一个漂亮姑娘
A pretty face...
查不到名字  出生记录
...with no name, no birth record,
任何社会联系
no social attached to it.
她是他们中的一员
She's one of them.
而且她为你工作  是吧
And she works for you, right?
你要怎样才肯不透露出去
What do I need to do to keep this quiet?
你知道我想要什么
You know what I want.
好吧  他们说得对  你很危险
Fine, they're right... you're dangerous.
我也危险  但那不代表你的为人
I'm dangerous. But that's not who you are. You...
你错了
You're wrong.
-我了解真正的林肯  -你不了解
- I know the real you, Lincoln, and you... - You don't.
我杀了我唯一的朋友
The man ?who killed his only friend,
一次次选择堕落
Who had to be saved from himself over and over?
这才是真正的我
That's the real me.
真实的我
That's who I really am.
我遇见你时你不是
Not when I met you.
你给了我希望  在这世上的一席栖身之地
You gave me hope, a place in the world.
看看结果如何
Look what happened to it.
你比谁都更了解
You know better than anyone,
如果你身边的一切都毁了  那问题就在你
if... if everything around you crumbles, then you're the cause.
够了
Stop!
你看不清  但我看的明白
You don't see it, but I do.
你帮助他人  因为那是你的使命
You... you help people because you were meant to.
你跟我们走就能帮助他人
You can do that with us,
就像你之前在医院那样  拯救生命
like you were doing at the hospital... saving lives.
那样的生活已经结束了
That part of my life is over.
不  你没有被诅咒
No, you... you are not cursed.
你不是什么可怕的东西
You are not some horrible thing.
我确定
I know...
因为你当初就是这么跟我说的
Because you taught me that I wasn't.
你让我相信我有使命
You convinced me that I had a purpose,
让我相信我的人生没有结束
that maybe my life wasn't over,
而只是有了新方向
but just... getting somewhere.
让我也给你这样的希望吧
Please let me do the same for you.
你担心我就是浪费时间
You're wasting your time caring about me.
我没法不担心
I can't help it.
我可以跟你走
I'll go in with you.
但我不会跟神盾局合作  我是跟你合作
I'm not agreeing to work with S.H.I.E.L.D., but with you.
我们会一起解决的
We'll figure it out together.
太好了  撤离准备好了吗
Great. Is the, um, escape module on its way?
计划有变
Change of plans.
科尔森的命令
Coulson's orders.
我们要把他交给ATCU
We're turning him over to the ATCU.
给科尔森打电话
Get Coulson on the phone.
他说回总部他会跟你解释
He said he'd explain back at headquarters.
黛西  怎么回事
Daisy, what's happening?
科尔森让我告诉你  他不会有事
But Coulson told me to let you know that you're gonna be safe.
他已经安排我们在旁观察确保...
He's arranged for us to observe and make sure...
我们能不能赶紧的
Can we get on with this?
这太过分了
This is crazy!
他说他没有选择
He said ?he didn't have a choice.
拿下他
Take him into custody.
疑犯逃跑了  封锁街道
Suspect's on the move. Seal off the street.
等待命令
Awaiting orders.
-我们去追他吗  -不
- Should we go after him? ?- No.
抓手到擒来的  拿下她
Bird in the hand. We take her.
你们想干什么
What the hell do you think you're doing?
遵从命令
Following orders.
你真以为你能拦得住我吗
Do you really think you can stop me?
你知道我能做什么吗
Do you have any idea what I can do?
嗯
Yeah.
所以我们在外面安排了三个狙击手待命
That's why I have three snipers outside, ready to engage.
你的异能范围有多远
What's the range on these powers of yours?
有多厉害
How good are they?
其实  还真挺厉害
Actually, pretty damn good.
把你的人叫回来
Tell your men to stand down.
不行
I can't do that.
他逃了  而我已经打了包票
He got away, ?and I've made assurances.
我向你保证  你如果非要抓我的特工
I assure you that if you insist on taking my agent in,
只会引发战争
you will start a war.
我会动用神盾局的全部资源和人力
I will devote all the resources and manpower of S.H.I.E.L.D.
摧毁你们机构
to crushing your agency.
不是针对你  只是工作
It's not personal. It's work.
我现在必须拿出成绩来
And right now I need to show results.
如果我给你更好的呢
What if Ii offer something better?
收到
Copy that.
看来今天算你走运
I guess it's your lucky day.
任务结束
We're done.
我们走
Let's go.
我觉得带你来个高档安静的地方
I thought it'd be good for you to get out somewhere nice...
会比较不错
and quiet.
人都哪去了
Where is everyone?
我确保了不会有人分你的心
Well, I made sure you wouldn't have any distractions.
菲兹先生  见到你很高兴
Mr. Fitz, ?we're delighted to see you.
你们的桌子就在这边
Your table is this way.
酒是赠送的
The wine is a gift from us.
这位年轻人真是有耐心
A very persistent young man here.
我们已经为他保留了几个月的预定了
We've been holding ?this reservation for months.
很高兴你们终于来了
I'm delighted you're finally here.
你一直留着预定
You kept the reservation.
别大惊小怪啦  没什么的
Don't make a fuss. It's not a big deal.
我记得我住院数月后你带我出去吃饭
I remember when you took me out after months in the hospital.
让我觉得又像个人了
It made me feel like a human being again.
那次你一直抱怨个不停
You complained the entire time.
好吧
Well...
坏脾气的人
Okay, a crabby human being.
真太感谢你了
I can't thank you enough.
嗯  这餐厅不错  是吧
Yeah. It's a nice restaurant, isn't it?
是啊  但不止如此
Yeah, ?but for more than that...
还有谢谢你找到我
for finding me.
我还能怎么办
What else was I gonna do?
我不知道该说什么好
I don't know what to say.
你什么都不用说
You don't have to say anything.
决定好要点什么了吗
Have you decided what you'll be having?
天呐  好多...
Oh, gosh. So much...
选择
to choose from...
或许这能帮你拿主意
Maybe this will help.
我敬杯酒吧
Should I make a toast?
怎么了
What?
能给我们点时间吗
Can you give us two minutes?
当然
Of course.
给我解释一下
Help me understand.
那个决定并不容易
It was not an easy decision.
把林肯交出去
To hand Lincoln over?
我必须做出选择
I had to make a choice.
不是我就是他
So it was him or me.
他们有你的照片  黛西
They have your picture, Daisy.
那他们怎么没抓走我
So why didn't they take me?
林肯一逃  你是怎么说服他们不抓我的
Once Lincoln left, how did you convince them not to take me in?
我给了他们一样有价值的东西
I offered them something just as valuable.
-什么  -我  我的专业知识
- What? - ?Me. My expertise.
怎么  我们还要跟他们合作了吗
So... so now we're working with them?
我不想再跟人
I'm done fighting with people
争谁来打击真正的敌人了
over who gets to fight the real fight.
这太浪费时间和资源了
It's a colossal waste of time and resources.
我对付过塔伯特
I went against Talbot.
我对付过神盾局的另一个派系
I went against another faction of S.H.I.E.L.D.
我们了解情况  他们不了解
We know what we're doing... they don't.
希望他们能跟我们学学
Hopefully, they can learn from us.
他们抓捕我的族类  我很难信任他们
It is hard to trust them when they are hunting people like me.
我没说我信任他们
I never said I trust them.
很好
Good.
别信任他们  我们并不知道他们的真正目的
Don't, because we have no idea what they're really after.
了解了  听我说
Duly noted. Look...
我知道这事触及了你的感情
...I understand this is a personal matter for you.
麦克把他听到的话告诉你了
So Mack told you what he heard me say?
什么话
And what would that be?
是罗莎琳
?It's Rosalind.
都直呼其名了啊
First-name basis, huh?
不打扰了
I'll leave you to it.
没想到你这么快就打过来了
Well, I'm surprised to hear from you so soon.
就是确认一下
Just checking,
看你是不是给了我假号码
making sure you didn't give me a fake number.
没事吧
You all right?
不怎么样
I've been better.
谢谢你没说出去
Thanks for not saying anything.
知道吗
You know what?
我需要点支援呢
I sure could use some backup.
看看你本事怎么样  丫头
Let's see what kind of skills you got, kid.
好吧
All right.
要见你可真不容易
Well, you certainly don't make it easy to get a meeting.
老大的要求
The boss doesn't want it to be easy.
但他总是愿意见
But he's always interested in meeting people
能证明自己的人
who can prove themselves.
他听上去挺有意思
Sounds like an interesting bloke.
很期待哪天见见他
I look forward to meeting him someday.
西蒙斯
Simmons?
你研究那个干什么
Why are you looking at that?
我想理解
Trying to understand.
这没什么值得研究的
There's nothing to learn from this.
它并没失效
It's possible it's not inert.
外星金属的特性很不一样
Alien metals ?have different properties.
我们无法确定
We don't know for sure.
我们能确定
Yes, we do.
你安全了
You're safe.
那个传送门不会再开启了
That portal won't open again.
但它必须开启
But it has to.
我得回去
I have to go back.
漫威影业出品
神盾局特工
第三季 第三集
本字幕由ZiMuZu原创翻译  最新下载请登录www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译 煮粥达人   苏小黛   Silence   SophiaSaaaga   milkon
翻译 杏仁斯嘉丽   珈美   盐湖嗨爪凉开水   王大可   彼岸的宁静
翻译 发糖开心草   时间轴 好油油   永远的永远   后期 宝宝
校对 这糖有点苦草   总监 不过还是好开心草
最新美剧下载请登录字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv
扫描左边二维码关注我们的微信号
或搜索微信号: ustvboom
非常欢迎爱好者加入字幕组一起翻译海外影视剧